# **EUGENE GARRETT**

### **Full Stack Developer**

@ eugenegarrett.dev0614@gmail.com

O Houston, TX, United State

#### **SUMMARY**

I have been working as a full stack developer for 8 years now. My main skills are React, Next.js, Node.js, Java and I have gained great experience in software development. I have gained a reputation as a trusted advisor and a valuable asset to any organization due to my ability to identify growth opportunities and tackle complex challenges. I can say that I am a creative, calm, detail-oriented person who loves to learn from others. My hobbies include soccer and occasionally playing computer games with friends. I am actively looking for a new job as a full stack developer and am ready to work for you immediately! Thank you.

### **EDUCATION**

04/2012 - 08/2016

Bachelor of Software Engineering
University of Calgary

## **EXPERIENCE**

10/2021 - 05/2024 •

Senior Full Stack Developer

San Gabriel, CF, USA

**PayrLink** 

PayrLink is a decentralized application powered by Blockchain technology that works as a decentralized third-party arbitrates transactions in a private manner from very simple and highly complex ones.

· I've been working with modern front-end frameworks using React, Next.js.

05/2018 - 10/2021

Senior Full Stack Developer

San Gabriel, CF, USA

WizardsDev

WizardsDev is a software development company that provides clients with technical

· I've been working with modern front-end frameworks using React, Next.js.

11/2016 - 04/2018

Junior Web Developer

Benevity, in Calgary

**Benevity** 

Benevity is a technology company that specializes in corporate social responsibility (CSR) and employee engagement solutions.

· They provide a platform that helps businesses manage their charitable giving, volunteer programs, and other social impact initiatives

### **SKILLS**

Jira	Git	React	Next.js	Тур	pescript	Express.js	Node.js	Solidity	Rust	Web3.js
Ether.	js I	Hardhat	Truffle	ERC	20 / ERC72	1 / ERC1155	Solana	Telegram	Bot	TailwindCSS
MUI	Fign	na Mo	ngoDB	Java	JavaScrip	ot C++	React Nativ	e		

### **LANGUAGES**

English Proficient

